Going to the Holy Land
I have a cold!
I have a cold, I have a cold, I have a cold
I've got a cold, I've got a cold.
Oh, God.
Here.
Let's go for it.
Look at this.
Uh-oh.
Eee...
Uh-uh.
Mmm. - Mmm.
This one.
Mmm-hmm.
Phew.
Ahh.
Hmm.
Phew!
ah ah ah ah ah
Me.
Tantantantantantantantantantantantantantantantantantan Hello everyone, sk 48 team s I'm Himeka Arano, aka Hime-tan, and this time I'm here in front of the SKE48 theatre in Sunshine Sakae, which is well-known to SKE48 fans.
SKE48 Theatre.
The members don't usually come this way.
The reason why I'm here is...
I'm Himeka Arano.
I'm going to the holy place.
This time.
It's a song by SK48.
Aichi Prefecture.
This time, from the SK48 theatre here.
I'd like to go there.
The showroom event that took place last year.
I was in the final audition for SKA.Y.
Thanks to the support of all the fans
I won first place.
I'm going this time because of that commitment.
Road biking is my hobby.
I usually ride it a lot.
This time, I'll be riding the longest distance of my life.
I'm really nervous.
I'll do my best!
I'm off then.
Bye-bye.
Okay, I'm off.
From the Alano Himekawa SK48 Theatre.
Journey to the destination
Let's get started!
Let's go for it! I'm off!
All right, let's go!
Start!
Ah!
Sunshine Sakae.
This is my first time running through Sakae.
I'm expecting to run about 70km this time.
I'm a bit worried about how it's going to go by the end.
I'm borrowing a Go-Pro, and this will be the first time I'm filming with it.
I don't really know how to use it anymore.
I don't really know how it works, but I think I know that the GoPro is very close to the camera.
I know that I'm really close to the GoPro right now.
But it's windy today.
I guess it's perfect like this.
Behind here is the Nippon Tokushu Toryo Hall.
Forest Hall.
Atsuta Shrine
We SK48 had our coming-of-age ceremony at the Atsuta Shrine.
I also had my coming-of-age ceremony at the Atsuta Shrine.
I miss it a lot.
I love Astasinghe as usual.
I go there in private too.
We're heading south.
I've been getting lost a lot since a while ago.
I'm getting lost on the way.
It's going to take us longer to get there than we planned.
It's really windy.
It's taking the wheel like crazy.
Jealous.
We're at Lake Shinmai.
Wow!
Amazing!
It was supposed to rain today.
But we managed to keep it cloudy.
We managed to keep it cloudy.
That's great!
It's something I could only have filmed today.
We are running the day after the 28 Hour TV5.
Around here, there aren't many traffic lights, so it's really easy to run.
I think we're a bit closer to Tsunena station, but there's a place I'd like to visit, so I'd like to head that way!
Hm.
I found something bad!
Can you see it?
Let's go near there.
Janggang Nameg Pottery Trail.
I've been wanting to come here.
I saw a glimpse of it earlier.
I wanted to see Tokonyan.
And here, there are so many cute things everywhere.
Look at this!
The pedestrian crossing has paw prints.
So cute!
There's a mailbox with a deliveryman made of pottery on it.
Amazing.
It's flooded.
This is the Manekineko Street.
I think it's my favourite.
There's so much more.
You should visit, too.
There's more.
All cute!
Wow.
A toko-nyan.
And there's a little cat, too.
It's looking at Tokonyan.
Of course he is, if he's been watching you for this long.
You'd be surprised, wouldn't you?
That's where I was running earlier, isn't it, and you'd be surprised to see me with a raw head like that.
That's where I was running earlier, isn't it?
From there.
Wow.
Just walking around is so much fun.
Just walking around is a lot of fun.
There's so much to see.
And also...
I heard there's another amazing path called Tsuchikanzaka.
I'd like to go there.
Wow!
Doukan-zaka.
Here we are!
Wow, that group of people from the Ministry of Physical Education and Training are here!
That's the Ministry of Health, Sports and Welfare!
If anyone's here...
Just a reminder...
Amazing!
It's very atmospheric!
It was a pottery trail.
It was a lot of fun!
You should definitely go there too!
There's one more place I want to go.
I'm on my way there now.
Oh...
I see it.
We're here.
It's too cute.
Light blue torii gate.
I think it's rare to see a light blue torii gate.
I thought it would be a great colour match for my Bianchi.
That's where I wanted to go.
I thought for sure they'd match.
It's so cute!
I'll take a picture.
This is the Koi no Suijinja Shrine.
This one is for health, long life, good fortune and traffic safety.
Traffic safety is important!
So cute! I had a good night.
But this time...
I heard it was closed.
I couldn't go.
That's sad.
I used to come here before.
I thought I'd save it just in case.
Fish Square.
I'll come back next time.
I've been really triggering my sense of direction since a while ago, and I'm really lost.
Believe it or not, there are people who get lost even when they look at a map.
Please keep this in mind.
It seems that shops close early around here.
When you go there, you have to leave very early.
I have to leave very early, because it's only a few minutes from here.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
It's so nice to ride along the sea.
I'm going to Shonan with you.
I really like the sea.
I love the sea, just because it's next to me.
I can work so hard just because it's next to me.
I love the sea.
There are dragonflies, too.
It's nice, isn't it?
No.
Almost there
Almost there.
Almost there? Just a bit more? What?
Just a bit more.
I'm sure you've seen this before.
Big lobsters.
This is what it feels like to be on the Senda Peninsula.
I'll hang on till the end. See you later.
Okay, I'm going.
To the Holy Land.
Maybe... maybe... maybe not...
It's here at last... and if it's here at last... and if it's here at last...
It's finally here!
Well, I mean, you know...
The restaurant... Oh, wait a minute.
Is that diner where you eat clams under construction?
It's under construction.
Oh, it's gone?
It's gone.
I'm so sad.
I'll get over it.
Go on, then.
We're really, really close.
To the bullet point.
Here we go.
Here we are.
Hazumisaki.
This is the sacred place of SK48.
There's a monument near here.
I'd like to go there too.
Yes, ma'am.
So this is the stone monument of Hazumisaki.
This is the monument of SK48, yes, the bouncing point.
This is the sacred place of sk 48.
I've made a commitment to go from the sk 48 theatre to Bouncing Point on a road bike, and I've achieved it.
The audition for SKA-Y is one thing, but...
I still have many dreams that I want to fulfil.
And so is the SK48 selection.
I also want to work on this road bike that I love so much.
I'd like to work on this road bike too.
I'll keep working hard from now on.
In 2024, I'll be working as a model for s cute!
I'll be working as a model for the May issue of "s Cute".
I'm going to continue to support sk 48 Team sk 48 Team sk 48 Team sk 48 Team sk 48 Team sk 48 Team sk 48 Team sk 48 Team sk 48 Team sk 48 Team sk 48 Team sk 48 Team sk 48 Team
I'm really happy to be here, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
We're really glad to be here!
Thank you for watching the video so far!
Hello again!
I'm Arano Himeka, aka SK48 Team S HIMETAN!
Thank you so much to the management for allowing me to upload this video to the official YouTube!
After making the video, I thought...
I've learned how much I appreciate the presence of all the people involved and how amazing it is to be a part of this project.
And after experiencing the production side and being a performer
I'm really glad that I took on this challenge.
I would like to do something like this again, so if there are places you would like me to visit or projects you would like me to try, please let me know in the comments section.
I'm at the SKE48 theatre, which is the starting point for this video, but we, SKE48, perform almost every day at this SKE48 theatre in Sunshine Sakae!
I'm performing in Team S's 'Ai yo Kimi ni Ai yo Boku ni' performance.
And all the teams are shuffled around and various teams perform.
I'm appearing in the performance while holding hands.
If you like, please come and see us.
I'll be waiting for you.
Even if it's just for a minute...
If you think we're doing something interesting...
Please give us a high rating.
Thank you for your high rating!
And please follow us on social networking sites.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you for watching until the end.
See you soon!
And we look forward to following you on social networking sites.
Thank you for watching until the end.
See you soon!